onwardclick.com 2016-02-12

# CPL (Leads), CPA (Actions), CPC (Clicks) and CPV (Views) Exchange - Onwardclick->>

## Privacy Policy  
Last Updated on March 15 2013...

**Introduction**    
Onwardclick is committed to protecting your privacy. The privacy statement below describes our policy with respect to the collection and use of your personal information on this website. By using this website, you consent to the terms of our privacy statement and to Onwardclick (also listed as Onwardclick.com) processing personal information for the purposes stated below.  

**Collection of Your Personal Information**  

Onwardclick may require you to provide us with personal information if you would like to participate in certain activities available on, or benefit from services offered on, this website. We limit our requests for personal information to information we believe is minimally necessary to achieve our stated collection purposes. Personal information collected on this website is often limited to name, URL, e-mail address and telephone number but may include additional information when needed to provide a service you requested.

Also, in order to improve our services and the quality of the website, Onwardclick provides you with the opportunity to send us your suggestions by completing a "Contact Us" form which collects personal information such as name and e-mail address. Note that any comments or materials sent to us, including feedback data, such as questions, comments, suggestions and any other responses are deemed to be non-confidential. We have no obligation with respect to such responses, and Onwardclick shall be free to use, reproduce, distribute, publicly display and use in advertisement such comments and materials (in part or all) without reference to you personally. Onwardclick is also free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such responses for any purpose whatsoever.  

**Use of Personal Information Collected**  

Onwardclick uses your personal information collected on this website primarily for the following purposes:  

**  To deliver services, such as reviews, newsletters, events, training or services you request, special promotions, offers from our partners, purchase opportunities or information.  
**

**  To alert you to service updates, special offers, information, and other new services from Onwardclick or to forward promotional materials.**

**  To ensure our website is relevant to your needs and conduct surveys to enhance our services.  
**

**  To help us create and publish content most relevant to you by optimizing our services based on you location, name or preferences.  
**

**  To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our website when and as appropriate.  
**

**  To contact you in response to sign up forms such as "Contact Us" or "Request an Evaluation", "Request a Review", "Career Opportunities", "survey" and in any existing or future forms.**  

If you choose to provide us with your personal information, we may transfer that information to Onwardclick's affiliates and subsidiaries or to Onwardclick's third party service providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. By using this website, you consent to any such transfer of personal information outside of your country or jurisdiction.

Onwardclick occasionally hires third parties to provide certain services available on our website or made available on our behalf. We will only provide those third party providers the personal information they need to deliver their services, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Onwardclick may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on this website, protect and defend the rights or property of Onwardclick and its family of websites or act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Onwardclick employees, users of Onwardclick products or services, or members of the public.  

Onwardclick reserves the right to transfer personal information to third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process including, but not limited to mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or part of our assets.  

Onwardclick does not otherwise use, sell, rent, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third parties.  

**Use of Non-Personal Information Collected**  

Onwardclick uses non-personal information such as demographic data to analyze and develop marketing strategy and to determine how you found about us, your interests regarding our products and services and how to further improve this website based upon user data. We may share such non-personal data with third parties.  

**Opt-Out**  

Onwardclick provides you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive emails from us or updates regarding new services and products offered on this website or if you do not want us to share your personal information with third parties. The opt-out choice may be exercised at the points where personal information is collected by requesting to opt-out (typically in the comment box) or, when provided by clicking on the opt-out button.  

If you do not have exercised the opt-out option at the point where personal information is collected or when receiving information from Onwardclick via e-mail, you may also do it by contacting us at [optout@Onwardclick.com](mailto:optout@encontext.com) or by responding to the e-mail you received and including the words "opt-out" in the subject line. We will process your unsubscribe as soon as possible, however, note that in some instances you may receive a few more messages until the unsubscribe is processed.  

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**  

While Onwardclick does not use tracking, we may at any time use "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used to collect information about website activity. For example, when someone visits the website, a cookie is placed on the user's machine (if the user accepts cookies) or is read if the user has visited the website previously. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. If you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the website.  

Pixel tags and cookies may be used in email messages that we send you directly or via a third party. These pixel tags and cookies are used to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our website. For more information about the technology used to deliver our emails, or to set your browser to reject cookies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  

If you have agreed to receive emails from us, those emails may contain advertising about goods and services that we think might be of interest to you. In order to understand how our readers interact with the emails and the content that we send, we use pixels in the text in order to understand who has opened the emails that they have been sent. In order to provide our content in the most interesting way, we also use pixels to learn whether you can receive emails in text or html form. If you click on a link in the email, we may set a cookie on your browser. If you visit this website as a result of clicking on a link, we are able to understand how you interact with the pages of our website through the combination of the cookie and pixels set on the pages of our website. This enables us to understand what interested you in our emails and what did not, and what interests you about our website and what does not. We can then try to send you more interesting information in the future. Please note that this information is for our use only - we do not disclose or share this information with any third parties.  

Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our website and your web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain personal information for trends and statistics.  

**Third Party Links**  

This statement applies solely to information collected on this website. This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we have no control or influence over the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you to read such other websites' privacy statement in order to understand whether and how they process data about your visit to their site.  

**Access to Your Personal Information**  

Onwardclick provides you with an opportunity to access your personal information to ensure it is correct, accurate and current. To edit your personal information, please contact us via e-mail at [webmaster@Onwardclick.com](mailto:webmaster@encontext.com) or via mail as indicated at the bottom of this page.  

**Changes to This Privacy Statement**  

With effect for the future, Onwardclick reserves the right to change this privacy statement from time to time. When we do, we will also revise the "last update" date at the top of this privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you be placing a notice on this website.  

**Security**  

Onwardclick endeavors to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we do not warrant or represent that your personal information is completely safe from hackers and other security threats. If you have any questions about the security on this site, you can send an email to [webmaster@Onwardclick.com](mailto:webmaster@encontext.com).  

**Enforcement of This Privacy Statement**  

If you have comments or questions with respect to this statement, please contact us at [webmaster@Onwardclick.com](mailto:webmaster@encontext.com). or via mail to the following address:

Onwardclick.com   
A Division of EnContext Media LLC  
4100 Redwood Road, # 176  
Oakland, CA 94619
